<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aagama 2k18</string>
    <string name="changing_text_in_splash">Generating the fun..</string>
    <string name="changed_text">Loading the energy..</string>
    <string name="final_text">All Set to Go..!</string>
    <string name="nothing" />
    <string name="departments_string">Departments</string>
    <string name="countdownleft">Left for the exciting event to begin</string>
    <string name="about">To be abreast of recent developments and to provide a common platform to the budding technocrats from all over the country, to have knowledge shared and to explore new horizons in the concerned Engineering, Pharmaceutical and Management streams, Anurag Group of institutions is going to conduct Aagama 2K18 on 16th and 17th March, 2018. In the present scenario, professional education like engineering is demanding overall development from the students. A student is expected to acquire thorough technical knowledge along with other supportive skills. With this back drop,  technical papers are invited from all the corners of the country. All the papers will be peer reviewed. There are many events like Tech Quiz, Paper presentation, Project presentation, Robotics, Circruitrix, Inversion and many more.</string>

    <string name="paper_presentation_cse"><b><b>Description:</b></b>\nHere one can present his or her knowledge on various technical topics from the field of computer science linked to various fields.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Team of maximum 2 members is allowed.\n2) Cash prize for the winner is Rs.2000/-.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) B.Sravya(8374347735)\n2) J.Reena(9951021639)\n3) A.Surya Bhavana(7680089957)\n4) E. Pallavi\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_cse"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a platform where you can express your thoughts that you have but couldn’t express verbally. You can expose your talent and in-depth knowledge on interested areas in posters.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 2 members are allowed in a team.\n2) Only technical topics are allowed.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Kranthi(9347225574)\n2) Tejaswini(7337427990)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="idea_presentation_cse"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a platform to pitch your ideas which can turn into startups. Idea can be technical or non technical. This is the best platform to show your ideas and make them into startups. The presentation should contain the business problem, business idea, financial resources, targeted customers.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 3 members are allowed in a team.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sowmya(9951830016)\n2) CH. Mamatha(8790544557)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="web_design_cse"><b>Description:</b>\nThis event is about designing a website. CSE and IT students are eligible.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 3 members are allowed in a team.\n2) Systems with internet are given.\n3) The time limit is 4 hours.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Venkatesh(9542874404)\n2) Karthik(8008760730)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="project_expo_cse"><b>Description:</b>\nThis event is about giving a ppt regarding the projects the students have done. They can participate as an individual or a team. CSE and IT students are eligible.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 2 members are allowed in a team.\n2) PPT is compulsory.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Haswitha(8106047227)\n2) Sanjana(9515225517)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="bugsmash_cse"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a stage to step on and prove your testing skills where you can feel the urge to play with game of codes and bug fixes.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 2 members are allowed in a team.\n2) Programs are of C language.\n3) This is a timed contest.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Greeshma(9618723001)\n2) Suchetha(7416146233)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="android_club"><b>Description:</b>\nParticipants will be given with some set of real time scenarios and they need to develop UI of the application first and then comes the backend.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nNo. of Participants: 2 per team(maximum).\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) G.Likhitha(9542355551)\n2) P.Lavanya(9848983188)\n3) Rachana(9640865075)\n4) Vasanth(9948646868)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="firefox_club"><b>Description:</b>\nTest your skills in one of the most trending technologies(Python) across the world. There will be 3 levels of coding challenges that will test your competency in Python. The teams who will clear the initial two rounds will be qualified for the final round. The winning team will be given merit certificates and a memento and there are participation certificates for all the participants.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nMax members per team: 2\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sathwik(9676839303)\n2) Sowmya(8106056899)\n3) Shalini(9912040881)\n4) Shashi(8978175062)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="animation_club"><b>Description:</b>\nTo explore the creativity with in you for developing a new theme using Powtoon. There will be 2 levels of creating themes, the teams who will clear the initial round will enter the  final round. The winning team will be given merit certificates and a memento and participation certificates for participants.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nMaximum members per team:2\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Pavithra(9063779181)\n2) Pranay tej(7097712233)\n3) Poojitha(7780509199)\n4) Murali(9550158571)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="iot_club"><b>Description:</b>\nParticipants will be given a single real time scenario and they need to develop the solution(s) that makes the best usage of Internet.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Participants should bring their own equipment.\n2) Team Size: 1 to 3(Persons).\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)	Sai Charan U(9866404103)\n2) Sowmya Sri AK(8897720828)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="code_knockout"><b>Description:</b>\nThis Hackathon consists  of two rounds(Qualifier round and final round) where the participants have to provide the solution using any language for the given problem statement. Winner would be given merit certificate. Assured certificates to all the participants.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nParticipants qualified in the qualifier round will be eligible for final round. \n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sai Pranav(9291559303)\n2) Vishnu Priya(7093752623)\n3) Siri(8897791865)\n4) Varun(9177713450)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>


    <string name="technical_quiz_ece"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is an event to show your technical skills in Electronics and Communication and also to enhance your knowledge.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 2 members are allowed in a team.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) P. Vani(9247263359)\n2) Rakshit(8885519988)\n3) Swetha(7386858590)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="circuitrix_ece"><b>Description:</b>\nParticipant will be given an organized circuit to look at for about 30sec. Then, the participants will be given a bread board with components. They should connect the organized circuit as given before as soon as possible. The participant connecting the circuit quicker will be the winner.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 2 members are allowed in a team.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) SK.Nikhath(9573033175)\n2) Shwetha(9515875218)\n3) Anvith(8897454121)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="ram_and_rom_ece"><b>Description:</b>\nCircuit will be shown on a paper for a particular amount of time. The participant should remember all the values of the components present in the given circuit. Then, a circuit with no values will be given and the participant should write down all the correct values as shown in the previous circuit. Participant writing maximum correct values in minimum time will be rewarded.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 2 members are allowed in a team.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Geethanjali(7893112994)\n2) Shyadha(8919517962)\n3) Ramya(7780337715)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="paper_presentation_ece"><b>Description:</b>\nHere we propose a platform for the technical presentations with a thesis related to the department. Slides should strictly be confined to a maximum range of 12 to 15 with a  time period of 7 to 10 minutes. Send your papers to aagama2k18ece@cvsr.ac.in.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nNo. of participants: Maximum 3 members.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Harshini(9032689358)\n2) Naren(9502413135)\n3) Sailesh(9550107602)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="project_presentation_ece"><b>Description:</b>\nProjects that are done by the participants could be presented on the day of event. Projects are expected to be technical and related to the department. Plagiarism is strictly punished. Send your project details to aagama2k18ece@cvsr.ac.in.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nNo. of participants: Maximum of 2 members per project.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sai Praneeth(9493866507)\n2) Chandra Prakash(8106589018)\n3) Sri Ram(9059176656)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="robotics_presentation_ece"><b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Amoolya(9676904906)\n2) Sravya(7093138812)\n3) Balaji(9700643757)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_ece"><b>Description:</b>\nPosters related to the department’s technical subject could be presented. Only Hard copies are allowed to be presented. Send your posters to aagama2k18ece@cvsr.ac.in.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nNo. of participants: Maximum 2 members.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Asma(9515413226)\n2) T.Sahitya(9515746142)\n3) Naresh(8328134716)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>


    <string name="paper_presentation_eee"><b>Description:</b>\nHere we propose a platform for the technical presentations with a thesis related to the department.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nSlides should strictly be confined to a maximum range of 12 to 15 with a time period of 7 to 10 minutes.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sai Preetham(8328055947)\n2) Prabudatta Pradhan(8712277185)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_eee"><b>Description:</b>\nPosters related to the department’s technical subject could be presented.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Only hard copies are allowed to be presented.\n2) Maximum of 2 members area allowed in a team.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) G.Pavan Kumar(8985097383)\n2) M.Madhuri(9491335049)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="project_expo_eee"><b>Description:</b>\nProjects that are done by the participants could be presented on the day of event.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Projects are expected to be technical and related to the department.\n2) Plagarism is strictly punished.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Koundinya(9704685222)\n2) G.Krishna(8297890912)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="technical_quiz_eee"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is a quiz competition where participants are posed with questions strictly realted to the department\'s subjects and different knock out rounds.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) No.of participants: Max 3 per group.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) P.Vamshhi(9032808109)\n2) K.Charan(8801203739)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>

    <string name="project_presentation_civ"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is a description about the project which is by model presentation. One should give clear description about the project in specified time.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nNo. Of participants: max. 3 members.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) P.Rakesh(8341580539).\n2) S.Harsha Vardhan(9177055653).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="innovative_idea_presentation_civ"><b>Description:</b>\nOnly 5 minutes of time will be given to participants. One should be able to complete the presentation within the time limit.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Only one participant.\n2) He/She should complete the presentation on time.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Viyaja Durga\n2) Gomathi(7337519357).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_civ"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a special form of presentation which speaks itself. The idea behind the poster should be understandable without any explanation from the participants.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nTheme: Evolution of Concrete Skyscrapers.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Afreed(919848652900)\n2) Rahul(7075505498)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>

    <string name="mekbolt_mech"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a technical event which is based on assembly and disassembly of mechanical components which will be provided. It is a time based event.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Two persons per each team.\n2) Minimum of 3 levels.\n3) Complexity of components will increase as level increases.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Abhiteja(9515370164)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="mind_spark_mech"><b>Description:</b>\nAn event wherein participants will be quizzed on topics from the engineering world and more! The quiz involves pictures, words, descriptions and choosing correct options all revolving around technology. The difficulty increases with each level and it is the survival of the SMARTEST!\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) The individual participants will register and each phase will contain 6 participants.\n2) Each level will have 15 questions with words, pictures etc and participant with LEAST points will be eliminated. There will be 5 levels and every successive level gets difficult.\n3) The final round will be a one on one rapid fire round and the participant with maximum points wins.\n4) On day 2, the winners from day one will participate in the grand finale and we will have new phases too.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) VV. Santhosh Kumar(7893076104)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="paper_presentation_mech"><b>Description:</b>\n“Perfection is not attainable, but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence”. These best phrases by Vince Lombardi has lighten up our minds! It’s all about how you put your topic or present your topic infront of the audience. They see the way you present your topic, the way you put your point, your presentation style, your language and how promptly and effectively you answer their questions. Come up with innovative ideas!\n\n<b>Structure of the event:</b>\n1) Select a thesis and create suitable Abstract.\n2) Submission of Abstract (in a IEEE formatted word document) for not more than 300 words before review date and mail to aagama.mech2k18@gmail.com (MS word 2010 is recommended).\n3) Selected participants should submit a soft copy of the paper with Abstract in IEEE format to aagama.mech2k18@gmail.com.\n4) Winner is decided by a selected delegate invited from respective head of department.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of two authors.\n2) Presentation should be a maximum of 7 to 10 minutes.\n3) Based on the peering review of the abstract , few papers will be selected for presenting the paper.\n4) The oral presentation should be in the form of Microsoft Power Point slides to the maximum of 8 to 10 slides.\n5) The presentation is strictly confined to only technical topics.\nLAST DAY FOR THE SUBMISSION OF ABSTRACT:MARCH 12TH,2018\nNo . of days of event : 2\nFaculty coordinator:\nP.Saritha(9949672656)\nStudent coordinators:\nK. Rachana(8688668223)\nP. Suma Swetha(7893252344)\n\n<b>Organizers:</b>\n1) J. Vikas Reddy\n2) Md Zainul Abiduddin\n3) A. Someshwar Reddy\n4) P. Bhanu Rajeswari Devi\n5) Vishnu Kanth Loya\n6) V. Rachana\n\n<b>Registration fee :</b>\n100/-(per paper)</string>
    <string name="prayog_mec"><b>Description:</b>\nThe art of model making is to show case your skills of assuming and creating a 3D model from a 2D design. The main aim of this event is to provide students with some general advice on how to produce informative and architectural models. The important thing is to start with a clear purpose to your architectural model and then work out on what sort of model will be best to achieve your goal.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Time based event.\n2) Two participant  for team.\n3) Minimum of two levels.\n4) Charges applied.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) K.S. Sandesh(9640181003).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n60/- per team of 2.</string>
    <string name="design_execute_mech"><b>Description:</b>\nDessin Xecute which we design in the software design which design is given by event organizers and also design in the unique manner and technical.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Only one mem participate\n2) Only design using software\n3) Complete the design in given time.\nNo of days : 2 days.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) V. Ramakrishna (8297951434)\n2) T. Sairiteesh Reddy\n3) M. Veeram Reddy\n4) K. Srikanth Reddy\n5) P. Ramchandra\n6) E. Saikrishna\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="meet_your_thoughts_mech"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is for the technical interaction in which innovative ideas will be discussed in the event which can used above current generation technology.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Paticipate member max ( Two Mem).\n2)	Ppt form.\n3)	It should be innovative.\nNo of days event : 2 Days\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)v. Venkateswarlu (9581559912)\n2) V. Saimanichandra\n3) P. Surender\n4) Y. Nehanth\n5) N. Sandeep\n6) Amir Sohail\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_mech"><b>Description:</b>\n“Mistakes are the proofs that your trying”. These lines have enlighten up that our mistakes can become new ideas. This is technical event in which description should be given in brief in the form of posters. You can improve your technical knowledge and meet new people.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Maximum of 2 to 3 members.\n2) Presentation should be maximum of 5 to 7 minutes.\n3) The presentation is strictly confined to only technical topics.\n4) Any kind of indiscipline activity , the team will be disqualified.\nNo . of days of event : 2\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) A. Ganesh Kumar(7893922479)\n2) Jayant Kumar\n3) Praneeth\n4) Madhav\n5) Jashvitha\n6) Vani sri\n7) Shaivalya\n8) Pranav\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="mechanical_cards_mech"><b>Description:</b>\nIt\'s time to awaken the mechanical engineer inside you. Here is a platform to showcase your technical as well as management skills. This event is to test your teamwork reflexes, technical knowledge and awareness.\nThis event consists of 3 rounds-\n1) Unitech\n  2) Tom and Hurry\n  3) Fast and Curious\nStructure:\nRound 1- Unitech:\nEach team will be provided with a box which contains tokens with alphabet or letter or number on it. Any parameter or quantity is announced for which the team has to guess the unit.\nRound 2- Tom and Hurry:\nOne of the team members will be given a card which has a mechanical component\'s name or word which he has to enact and other person has to guess the word within the time limit and arrange the letters of the word.\nRound 3- Fast and Curious:\nA person is blindfolded and given shuffled letters. He/she has to arrange it as the second person directs to form a mechanical term.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) A team shall consist of 2 members.\n2) The participants shall not be allowed to use mobiles and other electronic devices.\n3) Audience shall not give any hints or clues to the competitors.\n4) Any kind of indiscipline activity the team will be disqualified.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\nByreddy. Viveknath Reddy(9542227924)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>


    <string name="code_maze_it"><b>Description:</b>\nCode Maze is an event which has two levels. The first level consists of a puzzle. When the puzzle is solved, output will be present. Next level is to write the code based on the output. The code is to be written directly in the editor. When the code is compiled, the given output must be displayed. The output must be same and accurate. There is a time limit for the event. Both the levels must be completed within 3 minutes. The outputs will be easy and can be written in basic C-language. The top 2 teams will be awarded with prizes. Event includes fun in solving the puzzle and knowledge in coding.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Each team consists of 2 participants.\n2) The time limit is 3 minutes.\n3) Both the levels must be completed within the given time-limit.\n4) The outputs must match(from the puzzle and the editor).\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Lalitha(8008033754)\n2) Pooja(7702250959).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="cascading_code_it"><b>Description:</b>\nCascading code is an event in which participants are given a flowchart of a specific program. Participant should write the program for the flowchart given in the given time.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Revanth(9491217430)\n2) Shravani(9440322200)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="code_sink_it"><b>Description:</b>\nThe event is all about technical word which is taken in the form of Riddles. We will give you a particular time limit and you guys to Solve those riddles in the given time limit and whoever solves max Riddles will be awarded with some prize money.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Two mem participation.\n2) Find the word in given time.\nNo.of days: 2 days\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Raviteja(9030456970)\n2) Niharika(9704439856)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="cpu_collab_it"><b>Description:</b>\nThis competition is designed for students to display skills in processor assembly with great precision and speed. All the components must be replaced back on the CPU and to the right positions. Participants will identify the different processor components and arrange them to a working CPU. Follow instructions to put together a Processor parts using the right components and tools.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Only one participant.\n2) Participants will have to assemble the CPU from the available components.\n3) Breaking of components strictly prohibited.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Ramu(7794964362) \n2) Sindhuja(9100376901)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="mobile_app_mock_up_it"><b>Description:</b>\nParticipants are supposed to come up with an innovative idea for an app. They do not need to have the knowledge of coding or programming. They have to do a presentation explaining their app (if possible show the wireframes and screen mock-ups). The judges will give marks based on the problem-solving thought process, creativity and friendly UI design.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nMaximum of 3 members are allowed in a team.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Vinusha(9515223965)\n2) Gautham(8187830901)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="paper_presentation_it"><b>Description:</b>\n“Perfection is not attainablea but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence”. These best phrases by Vince Lombardi has lighten up our minds! Itʼs all about how you put your topic or present your topic infront of the audience. They see the way you present your topics the way you put your pointa your presentation style, your language and how promptly and effectively you answer their questions. Come up with innovative ideas!\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nA team should consist of only one student.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Karthik(9848127464)\n2) Seethaa(9177741438)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_it"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a special form of presentation which speaks itself. The poster should be understandable without any explanation from the participants.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Varun(9052351767)\n2) Madhulika(8498020204).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>

    <string name="oral_presentation_pharm"><b>Description:</b>\nSend the abstract to aagama2k18pharmacy@cvsr.ac.in with the subject of format of ‘Abstract – your id.no – your name’. The topic is about Pharmacy.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nThe following things are considered:\n<b><i>1. Scientific Content(50%):</i></b>\n(1)Introduction and background with pertinent literature cited.\n(2)Objectives clearly stated and concise.\n(3)Materials and methods (study design) clear.\n(4)Results and discussion clear, concise and accurate.\n(5)Significance of results to field of study.\n<b><i>2. Presentation(50%):</i></b>\n(1)Organization.\n(2)Logical orders, minimum redundancy.\n(3)Smooth transitions between presentation slides.\n<b><i>3. Slides:</i></b>\n(1)Legible with large fonts, color contrast, no conflicting backgrounds.\n(2)Text with no grammatical errors; not excessively wordy.\nDelivery:\n(1)Clear and audible speech.\n(2)Eye contact with audience.\n(3)Effective use of figures and/or tables.\n(4)Effective use of time.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) J. Hema(9959245954)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_pharm"><b>Description:</b>\n1)A team should contain a maximum of 2 members. Submit an abstract with not more than 200 words, on or before 12:00PM 15th March, 2018)\n2) Topic-Pharmacy.\n3) Send the abstract to aagama2k18pharmacy@cvsr.ac.in with the subject of format -‘Abstract –your id. no – your name’.\n4) Please include your complete details (i.e. name, email id) in the abstract.\n5) The size of the poster should be of 1*1.\n6) The font size should be large enough, so that it can be readable from 1 meter distance.\n7) The font style should be Times New Roman or Calibri.\n8) The posters received after 12)00pm, 17TH March, will not be considered in the competition.\n9) The aspects considered in the competition are: Technical content of presenter, Presentation skills, Poster format and appearance.\n10) Topics are: Pharmaceutics, Pharmacology, Pharmaceutical analysis, Pharmaceutical Chemistry, Pharmacognosy, Regulatory affairs, Hospital Pharmcy,Industrial Pharmacy.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Manisha(8121815435)\n2) Sowmya(7032289377) \n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="pharm_quiz_pharm"><b>Description:</b>\n It is a quiz based on Pharmacy subject.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Each team will comprise of 3 candidates.\n2) The quiz will have 1 Elimination round and 3 final rounds.\n3) 4 teams will be selected for final round.\n4) The last date of receiving the registration fee is 15th March 2018\n5) Elimination : This will consist of 15 objective questions which have to be solved in 5 minutes. 4 highest scoring teams will compete in the finals.\n6) The last 3 rounds will be played among 4 teams.\n7) <u>Finals: Consists of 3 rounds.</u>\n(1)First round: General questions and Visual Round.\n(2)Second round: Buzzer Round.\n(3)Third round: Rapid Fire Round.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sumander(9177465513)\n2) Bharathi(8978266048) \n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>

    <string name="paper_presentation_chem"><b>Description:</b>\nPresentation of your paper of any topic from your research.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Send your papers to aagama2k18chem@cvsr.ac.in\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Vinod(97034477162)\n2) Ashish(8885034514)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="poster_presentation_chem"><b>Description:</b>\nPresentation of research information usually in thee form of poster.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Send your papers to aagama2k18chem@cvsr.ac.in\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Prathima(9177628498)\n2) Jagan(8247513785)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="technical_quiz_chem"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is a game to test your knowledge about certain subject. They are usually used to determine a winner from a group of participants.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Haseeb(9640604662)\n2) Sneha \n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>



    <string name="circuitrix"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a series of competition where participants are tested with the knowledge of electrical circuits and their elements. It includes written tests with knock-out rounds and papers are evaluated by faculty judges.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nNo. of participants: 1 per registration.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) K.Pranay Kumar (8686406916)\n2) G. Navya (9989406848).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="code_cup"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a stage to step on and prove your coding skills. There are two rounds: \n1) 1st round:- Programs related to c, c++ will be given, participants need to find the bugs in the code, and MCQs within the time period. Groups solving the bugs and MCQs in time limit will be promoted to 2nd round.\n 2) 2nd round:- Two programs with the desired logic must be executed within the time period.\n 3) No electronic devices permitted like mobiles during the test.\n 4) Winner team would be given certificates and momentos.\n 5) Assured certificates to all the participants. \n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) There will be 2 rounds.\n2) Maximum of 2 people per group.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) P.Umeshchandra(9866239639)\n2) J.Chaitanya(8555879956)\n3) Dalchand Kumawat(8019330923)\n4) R.Dileep(8125583014)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n100/-</string>
    <string name="jigsaw_puzzle"><b>Description:</b>\nA puzzle will be given, but in a huge scale.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n A team should consist of two to three students.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sucharitha(9618662457)\n2) Swapna(7729087336)\n3) Pandu(7675869882)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n100/-</string>
    <string name="lan_gaming"><b>Description:</b>\nIt\'s a gaming event where students can participate as a team or as an individual. Games we are planning to include are NFS, CS 1.6 and more. Mobile game will be mini militia.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) A. Nikhil(7989145632)\n2) Vignesh(7337425305)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="model_making"><b>Description:</b>\nThe participants have to prepare any civil structure using the material provided by us. It is an ultimate opportunity for everyone to exhibit their architectural skills.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nA team should consist maximum of 2 members.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) G.Sneha(7013460127)\n2) Niharika(9676840325).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/- for single participant.</string>
    <string name="play_zone"><b>Description:</b>\nAs the title indicates the event is a non-technical event which includes games with mechanical components. It is a fun event where you can gain knowledge by playing games. It is a time based event. Participants will enjoy a lot in this event.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) There are 4 games in this event and it is of individual participation.\n 2) Each game has its own entry fee.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) V. Sharanya(7032398428)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="technical_thambola"><b>Description:</b>\nThis event is same as Thambola, but with a small twist. Instead of numbers, here we have some technical symbols.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) A team should consist of one student only.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Y. Prashanth(8309967749)\n2) Prathibha(8121899210)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="technical_power_hunt"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is non technical event where you can have fun with knowledge. It is just like a treasure hunt. We will ask a question related to power. If you answer you will enter into the power hunt. You can get knowledge along with entertainment.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) No. Of participants: Single player. \n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Bandari Shivani.\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="three_d_challenge"><b>Description:</b>\nWe will be giving a 3d view of isometric view in which the participant should analyse the top view, front view and side view of the 3d diagram. Open to the students of all departments.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Only one participant.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Y. Prasanna(8499088065)\n2) A. Akshaya Reddy(9154091184).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>

    <string name="brick_challenge"><b>Description:</b>\nWe will give you a soaked brick and you should hold the brick with only 2 fingers. There will be 5 members in the group. Participant who holds the brick for the longest time will be selected .\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) No of participants:1.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) N.shravya\n2) J.Anjali(9985748355).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="clay_moulding"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a platform where you can expose your skills on making some creative things with clay. You can showcase your talent and show your creativity. Certificate for all participants will be given.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)B.Vinitha: (7675868613)\n2)N.Indu: (9705445108)\n3)B.Maanvitha: (8328274043)\n4)G.Sai Anurag: (9666327381)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="creative_selfie"><b>Description:</b>\nExpose your creativity levels in taking selfies. Send us your best selfie and be the FB KING and the FB QUEEN. The participant will post their selfie to social media(FB) mentioning the page name (or) with #aagamaselfiee2K18) Then we’ll post the pic in the page. The participant whose selfie gets maximum number of likes will be the winner of contest.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) The selfie can be A simple one or edited.\n2) The selfie may be single, couple or group.\n3) The fake liker apps or websites are not allowed. If used, they will be disqualified.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Srujan Kumar(7730008285)\n2) Gangadhar Naik(9989636415).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n1) Single selfie:10/-\n2) Group selfie:20/-</string>
    <string name="dandiya"><b>Description:</b>\n\'Most popular in Gujarat\'. It is a special feature of the Navaratri festival. It is usually done in a group both by men and women. The special feature of the dance is the colorful attire worn by the dancers and the colourful sticks carried by them.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Sticks and traditional attire.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) G.Priyadarshini(8897605426).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="fabulous"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is a non technical event where you need to show that your an encyclopedia. We will give you a topic and you have to write 15 words related to that topic. It is time based. You can improve your knowledge and test your depth of reading.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) No. Of participants: Single player.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) A.Greeshma\n2) K.Apoorva\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="king_of_dice"><b>Description:</b>\nWe will provide some set of games in a room (dice based games like animal race, less-than or greater than 7). There will be some levels. Participants should complete each level to enter the next level.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) No of participants:1.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) CH.sneha Priya \n2) K.Priyanka(7207478737).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="matlab_mania"><b>Description:</b>\nParticipant will be given a matlab code. Participant has to type the code while the monitor is off. As the code is typed, the code will be executed and the participant typing the code in less time with minimum amount of errors will be rewarded.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nA team should consist of only one student.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Blessy(9032695974)\n2) Bindu Sri(9515368008)\n3) Sowmya(9848427981)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="mirror_walk"><b>Description:</b>\nThe participant will be provided with a mirror of normal size. By looking into the mirror the person must walk reverse in the path provided. The person who completes the task in the least time will be announced as the winner.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Only one individual can play the game.\n2) He/She should not turn head during the game.\n3) He/She must walk reverse by looking into the mirror only.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) CH. Venkatamani Kumar(8179074489)\n2) M. Yashwanth(7396039989).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="mock_cid"><b>Description:</b>\nBe a detective and chase the case. The mystery room brings you the ultimate excitement in the process investigation. In the mystery room the participants have to suspect the things and they have to narrate the mystery in a given time specified for each group or a person. Finally, prizes will be awarded according to the best narration of chasing the mystery case.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Cell phones are not allowed.\n2) Maximum team can be of 2 members.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) G. Yathish(9553270069)\n2) V. Sandeep(8374430954)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="painting"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a platform where you can expose your talent on art . To participate in this event you need not be an artist, your interest to make a painting is enough. You can explore your creative ideas here. In this event we are going to teach you Meenakari painting, Coffee painting and Glass painting.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sowmya(9494541728)\n2) Nandini(9948737461).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="rangoli"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a platform where you can showcase your talent and prove that we are not only proficient in the technical terms but also in non-technical events.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Max of 2 members are allowed in a team.\n2) Participants should get their own material.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Srinija(9515952379).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="break_it_if_you_can"><b>Description:</b>\n It is a non technical event related to puzzles. The task is to solve the puzzles. You can improve your problem solving skills. Develop your critical thinking.</string>

    <string name="code_breakers"><b>Description:</b>\nSome hints will be given about a word and the participant should guess the word.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nA team should consist minimum of one student and maximum of three students.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Vinay kumar(8639154726)\n2) Nanditha(8374012854)\n3) Ajay(88974541217)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="devil_follows"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is an innovative game which would give students a lesson on how to work in a team and create team building attitude among them. In this event, a group of four students would be given a task. Out of 4 members, 3 would be blind-folded and fourth member can’t speak.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sai Kushal(9154721151)\n2) Sai Deep(9948942424)\n3) Niharika(8885456577)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="dumbshell_electronics"><b>Description:</b>\nThis event is same as Dumbshell arts, but with a slight twist.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nThe team should consist minimum of two students and maximum of three students.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Bhavana(8142704072)\n2) Ch.Kavya(9985866673)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="inversion"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is completely a fun based non technical event. As the name itself says that it is inversion type. Explore your world in the mirror world. It has several tasks which should be completed in a limited period of time. You can have a lot of fun and improve your creativity.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) No. Of participants: 2 members a team.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Cholleti Navya\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30 for single game and 100 for all games.</string>
    <string name="word_wrap"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is a non technical event related to words where you can test your vocabulary. We have several rounds with different types of games. It is a time based event. You can gain knowledge. It tests your speed of thinking and reaction time.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Only one participant.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) B. Shiva Kumar\n2) V. Harsha Snigdha\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="fun_carnival"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is completely a fun based(non-technical)event. There will be several tasks which should be completed in a limited period of time.It is playful and super exciting.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1)Event comparises of 4 rounds or games.\n2)Individual participation for each round.\n3)Difficulty of game increases round by round.\nNo . of days of event : 2.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) G. Vamshi(8985141583)\n2) R. Eshwar\n3) C S Sai Shiva Kumar\n4) A. Pramodh\n5) S. Shiva Shankar\n6) K. Kumar\n7) D. Akash\n8) C. Navyasri\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>

    <string name="virtual_job_fair"><b>Description:</b>\nVirtual Job Fair is something new and exciting. The event explains the hiring process and stands as easy access to get knowledge about interviews. It is an open forum which involves great interaction with candidates where doubts and queries are clarified. Thus goes without saying that it would be a nice experience for students who appear for interviews in future.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Shreya(8106518261)\n2) Arshad(7675978926).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="words_worth"><b>Description:</b>\nWe\'ll have all the participants come with a paper and display one big word on the screen at a time. Participants have 60 seconds to write as many small words from the one big word as possible in those 60 seconds. This will repeated for at least 5 rounds. The one with highest word count of legitimate words (with letters only from the one big word) wins!\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Vaishnavi(7680088567)\n2) Nanda(949263408).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="deadly_hunt"><b>Description:</b>\nA treasure hunt is one of many different types of games with five or more players who try to find hidden objects by following a series of coding clues. Treasure hunt game is an outdoor activity.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Harish(7793997937)\n2) Bhavana(958114623).\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>

    <string name="best_out_of_waste"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a platform where you can expose your skills on making best out of waste. People participating will be given waste papers, straws etc and they will be asked to make best things from them. People doing the best thing will be awarded. Certificate for all participants will be given.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) M. Maneesha(9030407062)\n2)P. Sai kiran(8501011595)\n3) R. Nandini(9703349914)\n4) B.Sukanya(8897589352)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="dham_laga"><b>Description:</b>\nPulling the rope.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) No inappropriate language will be tolerated.\n2) Please wear proper athletic shoes - NO CLEATS!\n3) Gloves may be worn.\n4) Players may only pull for one team.\n5) A single team may consist of minimum 5 players.\n6) No wrapping the rope around any body part during pull.\n7) First team to pull mid-rope marker 6ft. beyond midline is the winner.\n8) Direction of pull will be decided by a coin toss.\n9) Starting cues : “Take the strain” (teams pick up rope, prepare)\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Manoj(995182299)\n2)  Kavitha(8501085572)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="filmy_quiz"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a quiz on films.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) Each team will comprise of 3 candidates.\n2) The quiz will have 1 Elimination round and 3 final rounds.\n3) 4 teams will be selected for final round.\n4) The last date of receiving the registration fee is 15TH March 2018 with a Demand Draft of Rs.300/- (group of three students)\n5) Elimination : This will consist of 15 objective questions which have to be solved in 5 minutes. 4 highest scoring teams will compete in the finals.\n6) The last 3 rounds will be played among 4 teams.\n7) Finals : Consists of 3 rounds\n8) First round: General questions and Visual Round\n9) Second round: Buzzer Round\n10) Third round: Rapid Fire Round\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Vasundhara(9100214050)\n2)  Sahithi purna(8125479573)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="gift_unwrapping"><b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Yashasvi(8179451959)\n2) V. Vyshali(9696935175)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="gol_gappa"><b>Description:</b>\nPanipuri challenge\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) You have to eat as many pani puri as possible in 60secs.\n2) Pani puri will be provided.\n3) Our coordinators will count the number of pani puri eaten.\n4) The wastage done will also be accounted for in deciding the winners.\n5) Re-Registrations of the team shall not be allowed.\n6) Team once registered cannot be changed.\n7) The decisions of the respective authorities would be final and binding for all the participants.\n8) The winners will be announced and rewarded the same day only.\n9) Be ready for surprises, twists and turns as a part of the competition.\n10) The members participating shall do so at your own willingness and management shall not be responsible for any health / physical related issues irrespective.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Rakesh(95428873737)\n2)  S.Pranathi(9603914314)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n25/-</string>
    <string name="lucky_draw"><b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Sai Teja(9160160755)\n2) Don andrews(9700034296)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n20/-</string>
    <string name="pharma_treasure_hunt"><b>Description:</b> Treasure hunt\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\n1) The Treasure Hunt consists of number of clues, each one leading to one or more treasures. \n2) At each treasure location, except as noted in rule #3, there are four slips of paper –one of each team\'s color. Find your team\'s colored treasure and turn it in at your team\'s headquarters. Then turn in the treasure at Treasure Hunt headquarters and tell which clue led you to that treasure. If you correctly match treasure and clue, your team will be awarded the points for that clue. Each team is allowed only three guesses at which clue a given treasure matches; after the third incorrect guess, the treasure is discarded. All treasures have been marked for identification, but these markings are generally insignificant to teams. The treasures with significant markings, such as those for clue #30, will always be identified in the clues.\n3)  The points awarded for clue #50 are not necessarily dependent on the handing in of colored pieces of paper. Treasures associated with clue #30 are marked with letters to be exchanged for the correspondingly-lettered word clues for the double crostic. \n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Swathi(9573440184)\n2)  Akshay(7032302532)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="puzzle_break"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is a non technical event related to puzzles. Task is to solve the puzzles. You can improve your problem solving skills. Develop your critical thinking.\n\n<b>Rules:</b>\nNo. of participants: Single player.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) P.Madhuri sree\n2) M. Manusha \n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="rope_tieing"><b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Rakshandha(9515044718)\n2) Pravalika(9704040377)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="save_me"><b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Alekhya Reddy(9441209107)\n2) Dakshayini(7337057273)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="slow_cycling"><b>Description:</b>\nContestants should ride the cycles as slow as possible without falling down.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Syed Ismail(7416276730)\n2)  Prathyusha(9100194180)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>

    <string name="chem_treasure_hunt"><b>Description:</b>\nPlayers are given hints to find hidden objects.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Shiva(7013958360)\n2) Shwetha(9963928701)\n3) Shree\n4) Kavya\n5)  Divya \n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="compound_preparation"><b>Description:</b>\nThis is a procedure where guidelines are given to prepare a certain compound and the person obtatining maximum yield is declared as the winner.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Shoaib(8374304452)\n2)  Anusha(9100545381)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n50/-</string>
    <string name="film_quiz_chem"><b>Description:</b>\nQuestions about movies,fictional characters are asked.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Mahinder(9010697990)\n2) Vinod(9703477162)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="rubix"><b>Description:</b>\nPerson who solves the puzzle in the given time is declared as the winner.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1)  Kavya .B(9032551575)\n2)  Pratima(9177628498)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>
    <string name="spell_bee"><b>Description:</b>\nIt is a classic word game in which one test their knowledge of words.\n\n<b>Coordinators:</b>\n1) Hajira(9618389366)\n2)  Beulah(9493570419)\n\n<b>Registration fee:</b>\n30/-</string>



</resources>
