<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aagama 2k18</string>
    <string name="welcome_in_splash">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="changing_text_in_splash">Generating the fun..</string>
    <string name="changed_text">Loading the energy..</string>
    <string name="final_text">All Set to Go..!</string>
    <string name="home_screen">HomeScreen</string>
    <string name="nothing" />
    <string name="department">CSE Department</string>
    <string name="departments_string">Departments</string>
    <string name="countdown">There are only</string>
    <string name="countdownleft">Left for the exciting event to begin</string>
    <string name="about">
        To be abreast of recent developments and to provide a common platform to the budding technocrats from
        all over the country, to have knowledge share and to explore new horizons in the concerned Engineering,
        Pharmaceutical and Management streams, Anurag Group of institutions is going to conduct Aagama 2K18 on
        16th and 17th March, 2018. In the presert scenario professional education like engineering is demanding
        overall development from the students. Student is expected to acquire through technical knowledge along
        with other supportive skills. With this back drop technical papers are invited from all the corners of
        the country. All the papers will be peer reviewed. Many events like Tech Quiz, Poster presentation, Project
        presentation, Robotrix, Circruitrix, Velocity, Invasion, Lazer Trap and many more.
    </string>
    <string name="paperpresentation"> An investment in knowledge pays you best interest. Do you have good knowledge? Are you good at presentation? Then come and show us. This is also an opportunity to win certificate and cash prizes. Do not miss it.</string>
    <string name="poster">This is a platform where you can express your thoughts that you have but couldn’t express, you can expose your talent and in depth knowledge on interested ares in posters.</string>
    <string name="idea">This is a platform to pitch the ideas which can turn upinto startups. Idea can be technical or non technical . this is the best platform to sow your ideas and grow into startups.</string>
    <string name="web">This event is about designing a website. CSE,IT are eligible.</string>
    <string name="expo">This event is about giving a ppt regarding the project the students have done. They can participate as an individual or a team. CSE and IT are eligible.</string>
    <string name="bug">This is a stage to step on and prove your testing skills where you can feel the urge to play with game of codes and bug fixes.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_technical_quiz">technical_quiz</string>


</resources>
